stansberryresearch.com 2008-10-12

# Stansberry & Associates Investment Research - Privacy Policy

| ****  
---  
  | True Wealth  
  | Porter Stansberry's  
Investment Advisory  
  | S&A Oil Report  
  | Advanced Income  
  | The 12% Letter  
  | Sjuggerud Confidential  
  | Phase 1 Investor  
  | S&A FDA Report   
  | S&A Prospector   
  | Extreme Value  
  | S&A Short Report  
  | Inside Strategist  
  | S&A Dividend Grabber   
  | International Strategist  
  | Quant Trader  
  | True Income  
  | The S&A Digest   
****  
  | Monthly Dividend Program  
****  
  | The S&A Alliance  
  | True Wealth Alliance  
  | Private Wealth Alliance  
  | Income Alliance  
  |    
|  | 

We take your privacy very seriously. If you have any questions on our privacy policy that are not addressed below, contact customer service at 1-800-261-2693, Monday through Friday, 9 a.m.-5 p.m. EST. 

**E-mail Address**

When you subscribe, your e-mail address is placed in a database and used to send your issues, special notices from the service or publication you subscribed to, and occasional advertisements. We will not add your name to our e-mail list without your permission. We will not sell, rent, or otherwise share your e-mail address with anyone. 

You can remove your address from our e-mailing list by following the instructions at the end of every e-mail we send.

**Personal Information**

We will never ask you for personal information – your credit card number, for example – except when you place an order. At that time, we will provide a secure (SSL, encrypted) connection and require you to submit only the information needed to complete and fulfill your order. Only our authorized employees will have access to this information. We will not sell or rent this information to anyone, nor share it in any other way, unless required to by a law enforcement agency that takes the proper steps to require it. Please note that "personal information" does not include your mailing address. See Mailing Address, below.

**Mailing Address**

When you give us your mailing address, we will use this information to fulfill your order or subscription and to send you information on other products that may suit your interests. If you don't want us to send you this other information, please contact our customer service department:

Attn: Customer Service  
1217 St. Paul Street  
Baltimore, Maryland 21202 USA

**Cookies**

Cookies are small files placed on your computer by a web page when you visit it. They can be used to store all sorts of useful information to make your next visit easier and more convenient, but some people are uncomfortable not knowing what information is in a cookie.

Stansberry & Associates web site only uses cookies to allow authentication for access to the Subscriber Only areas of our sites.

**Copyright and Disclaimer**

All contents of this website are copyright 2007 by Stansberry & Associates Investment Research. All rights reserved: Reproducing any part of this document is prohibited without the express written consent of Stansberry & Associates Investment Research.

DISCLAIMER: This work is based on SEC filings, current events, interviews, corporate press releases, and what we've learned as financial journalists. It may contain errors, and you shouldn't make any investment decision based solely on what you read here. It's your money and your responsibility. Stansberry & Associates Investment Research expressly forbids its writers from having a financial interest in any security they recommend to our subscribers. And all Stansberry & Associates Investment Research (and affiliated companies) employees and agents must wait 24 hours after an initial trade recommendation is published on the Internet, or 72 hours after a direct mail publication is sent, before acting on that recommendation.  
  
©2008 Stansberry & Associates Investment Research. All Rights Reserved. Protected by copyright laws of the United States and international treaties. This website may only be used pursuant to the subscription agreement and any reproduction, copying, or redistribution (electronic or otherwise, including on the world wide web), in whole or in part, is strictly prohibited without the express written permission of Stansberry & Associates Investment Research, LLC. 1217 Saint Paul Street, Baltimore MD 21202.
